[intense music playing]
That brooch. Is that Perry's?
How's it going with them?
Can we talk about your love life?
That sad bun reeks of boy problems.
Is this about Cam?
No, it's not him.
There's someone else?
I hooked up with Josh.
[laughing]
[both laughing]
-Wow. I cannot leave you unsupervised.
-No need to worry about that.
He's firmly in the past tense,
and I'm focusing on me and my rowing now.
-[intense music continues]
-[heavy breathing]
I was previously prescribed beta-blockers
for hypertrophic
obstructive cardiomyopathy,
but it's not enough
to keep up with my rowing.
You have HOCM.
And you want to keep rowing?
You understand
there's serious risks to that.
That's why I came here.
I heard you take specialized cases.
I will make it worth your while.
I never saw this report.
Mm-hmm.
And I never gave you
this medication, disopyramide.
It'll mitigate the risks
in the short term.
How do I get a refill?
You don't. It's a temporary fix.
It's only a matter of time
before it stops working.
[grunts]
Hey, Dad.
You know, I finished those oil changes.
Cool if I clock out, get some training in?
Sorry, bud, I still need you.
We're really behind,
and it's just you and me
for the next little while.
Okay.
I'll get my tools.
[sighs heavily]
[Britney] This is sad.
Like you don't hide a stash of Skittles
in your Pilates mat.
-[Baloo laughs]
-Yeah, yeah.
Being single is humiliating.
Humiliating?
Logan used me to sabotage the team,
and I fell for it.
This is the last day
we drown our feelings in snacks.
-No promises.
-Bronson, this is beneath us.
Binging on carbs is a cliché.
When did this happen?
What? Like it's hard?
I know you got hurt.
But the best way to get over a guy
is to crush them
and take everything they love
for yourself.
[machine beeping]
[trainer] Stay in the zone, Ryder.
This is how you wanted
to spend your weekend.
I didn't get to the Olympics
giving 95 percent.
-Who's got 100?
-Me.
You're slowing down. Who's got 100?
Me!
[Hayden] All right, crew. That's enough.
Glad you took my suggestion
to get a 2K in this morning.
The Norfolk Indoor Rowing Invitational
is coming up.
And only those
with strong erg scores qualify.
Now this year, as a bonus,
there will be a scout
for the junior national team.
And guess what? Cam, Josh,
Ryder, and Baloo.
You've made the cut.
-Yeah!
Let's go!
And on the girls' side, Teagan, you're up.
-No way!
-[Baloo] Nice, Tea!
-Time to show us what you can do.
-[Teagan laughs]
[rousing music playing]
You got a PR. Not bad.
-Looks like Cam's my only competition.
-[scoffs]
Well, enjoy this moment.
It's not gonna last.
Okay, everyone,
make sure to fill out your sign-up sheets.
This is an individual competition,
but we're still rooting for you all.
Can you pass the clipboard?
Saw you on the erg.
You're looking pretty good.
Yup.
Yeah, I guess I deserve that.
How long am I gonna get the cold shoulder?
Life is long.
[sassy EDM playing]
-[Baloo] Can I ask you something?
-Yeah, sure.
I saw the competition list.
Logan's gonna be there.
And I wanna kick his ass.
I love the fire. Okay?
But he's really good. Westvale's best.
I know. But…
I'm the hurt party, right?
So I deserve to beat him.
Well, I'm not sure about that logic.
Come on, you've been watching me, right?
What do I need to do?
He's got you flustered.
When you're flustered, you're messy.
If you come in hot,
you're going to burn out.
Don't let him get to you.
Okay. Okay, okay.
Yeah, I think I can do that.
-Yeah, you got it.
-Thanks, man.
Yeah.
-Hey, Mom.
-Hey.
I've got news.
-Mm?
-I'm invited to the Norfolk Invitational.
[gasps]
Amazing. Yes! [laughs]
-[phone buzzing]
-Oh!
[gasps] Hold on.
Richard, I got the flowers you sent
for my promotion.
You didn't have to.
Well, you kind of did, didn't you?
[Richard] President of Luxury Travel.
Congratulations.
I wanted the job,
but I'm actually glad that you got it.
You see,
everyone wants in on luxury travel,
including the other airlines,
so I convinced Dad to sell
you and the division off to the Dutch.
What?
Don't worry. You'll still have
a beautiful corner office
-in Rotterdam.
-[sinister music playing]
You snake.
Enjoy the windmills.
[gasps]
[phone clatters]
[exclaims]
[suppressed scream]
-Mom.
-He outplayed us.
We're on the outside now.
It's not fair.
Regis Airlines belong to us
as much as them.
Yeah, well, it'll be impossible
to get back on Viktor's radar now.
There's one thing
that Granddad can't ignore.
It's always burned him
that he never made it to the Olympics.
But I've got a shot.
The junior national team scout
is gonna be at the Norfolk Invitationals.
You'd be on track
to being the first Regis at the Olympics.
If I win.
Do whatever it takes.
[engine starting]
So this is where you live.
What do you want, Ryder?
You know, tomorrow's race
is down to me and you.
Pretty sure it's just me.
I've noticed you picking up extra shifts
here at the shop.
You help me, and I'll help you.
[uneasy music playing]
I need the scout looking at me tomorrow.
So… what's it going to take
for you to make that happen?
Are you asking me to throw the race?
I'm asking you… to name your price.
What do you want?
An erg? A vacation?
A car?
I can go higher.
Get out.
Everyone has a price, Dillinger.
[upbeat music playing]
[Ella and Hayden laughing]
Teagan?
Teagan.
-The coast is clear.
-Okay.
-I will see you later tonight. Okay?
I gotta get in the shower.
Wish I could join you.
[door opening]
-[Hayden] Oh! Uh…
-[Teagan screams]
-Oh my God! Coach Hayden…
-Teagan.
Why are you here?
-I-I-I can explain.
-With your shirt open.
Probably a conversation
for you and your mom.
Did you stay over with me in the house?
I should go.
Oh, this is so not cool!
See you at practice.
Mom!
-[groans] Oh my God!
-[door opens and closes]
[Cam's dad] Don't say there's nothing
you can do. You can give me more time.
I can get the 48K.
I heard you the first time.
Jackasses.
What's going on, Dad?
Oh, nothing you need to worry about, son.
$48,000 is a lot of money.
-Are we going to be okay?
-Look.
Whatever happens with the bank,
we're gonna be okay.
So just get out there,
and you show that scout
what you're made of.
-Okay?
-Mm-hmm, all right.
Knock 'em dead.
Rowers are divided
by age, schools, and rank.
All you gotta do is give them
their erg numbers and start times.
Then check them off here.
Explain again why I'm giving up
my Saturday to play attendance cop?
Because last Saturday, I went to
no less than six record stores with you.
And I saved you from the other four.
You're welcome.
-Thank you.
-[Teagan clears throat]
-Nice to see you again. Love the shirt.
-Love it.
And how it is completely on.
I'm gonna check with the refs.
I will see you inside.
Sorry, we ever formally met?
I'm Teagan. Our parents are dating.
-I'm Madison. And I already knew that.
-Wait, how long have you known?
It's been a few weeks.
Weeks?
So you're in race 2 on erg 14.
Oh, my… Weeks? What the hell?
Why didn't they just tell me?
I mean, in their defense, your reaction.
Come on, it is perfectly appropriate.
-I saw your dad's abs.
-Hey! Too far.
Exactly.
I'm not your enemy.
Some advice? There are five stages
to parents dating again.
Anger, denial.
Anger again. Then, "You're not my mom,"
and… finally, begrudging acceptance.
-[Cam] Madison.
-We locked in?
Running up stairs, eating raw eggs,
punching meat in the freezer?
No more Rocky marathons for you.
You're in race 1 at erg 10.
You got this, Dillinger.
Good luck out there.
Thank you.
-He's so different with you.
-Dillinger? Boy's same as ever.
How long have you guys been friends?
I've known him since his bowl-cut phase.
Ah. [laughs]
Yeah, he and I… used to be friends, but…
Barely talks to me now.
How can I fix it?
Look, he's going through his own thing.
It's him. He just needs some time.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Bronson Garner.
[clears throat] So you do exist.
Just here to race and take gold.
Good luck with that.
I know how easily you give up.
At least I don't cheat to win.
Ryder Regis.
[man] Um… You're in the first race. Erg 9.
-Thanks.
-Hey, there's the scout.
I read up on him.
He was the coach at Georgetown.
Make sure you mention
you're applying to his alma mater.
Obviously.
Me too. Who isn't applying to Georgetown?
Where's your dad?
He didn't want to watch you lose?
He's overseas on business.
Had to close on a deal.
Did you hear
someone's moving to, uh, Rotterdam?
Where even is that?
Let's go, Ryder.
May the best man win.
[intriguing music playing]
Teagan.
I know we're gonna have
to deal with this at some point,
but today I'm your coach,
and I expect you to treat me like one.
I think I get to decide.
Well, your coach has
intel on your competition,
which will help you impress the scout.
Do you wanna hear it?
Okay, fine.
No surprise here.
Gravenhurst are likely one and two.
But there is this up-and-comer from
Claremont that you gotta watch out for.
But if you keep pace on your third 500,
you have a shot at the top spot.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This doesn't make up for smashing my mom.
Okay, well, hearing that
is punishment enough.
Mm-hmm.
About your mom…
Okay. No PDA.
She is home by 11, and I am up at 6.
So please,
if you're sneaking out, go earlier.
Deal.
[woman over PA]
Five minutes until the U17 Men's race.
Teagan?
Hello?
-[David] It's just me.
-[gasps]
David.
What are you doing here?
El, I didn't mean to scare you.
I didn't think you were home,
but I just needed to get something.
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't call the cops right now.
Because this is gonna fix everything.
[intriguing music playing]
Ryder.
You trying to mess with my Zen, faid?
Would that deal still be on the table
if I wanted it?
How much?
48K.
It's a big ask.
So is tanking my shot at junior nationals.
Yeah, I can make that happen.
[tense music playing]
You sure about it?
You'll see in the race.
[woman over PA] All first-race rowers
to the floor, please.
[fast-paced music playing]
♪ Nobody gonna hold me back ♪
Can I have all the rowers
from the first race, U17 Men,
on their assigned ergs, please.
♪ Ain't nobody gonna hold me back ♪
♪ Nobody gonna hold me back
Nobody gonna hold me back ♪
♪ Nobody gonna hold me back ♪
-Go!
-Let's go, Ryder.
-Dillinger, right?
-Yeah, that's me.
Heard you might be one to watch.
-Have a good race.
-Thank you.
[driving EDM playing]
[woman] All competitors
are now on the floor.
♪ High blood pressure, they won't catch ya
Tap some extra here right now ♪
All rowers, pick up the handle.
Sit ready.
Attention… Go!
-[buzzer sounds]
-Let's go, boys!
[Teagan] Let's go, Easton!
[Hayden] Go, Easton!
Ryder's taking an early lead.
[Teagan] Pull! Come on, guys!
All right. Keep it up, Easton!
Baloo's making a move.
Baloo's pushing too hard.
He's gonna burn out.
[Teagan] He's letting Logan get to him.
[Hayden] Look at Josh. He's coming in hot.
[grunts]
[Madison] Josh is losing steam.
[Hayden] Josh is dropping.
[groans]
Come on, Cam!
[Madison] Let's go, boys! You got it!
[Teagan] Cam's in first! Whoo!
Go, Cam!
Cam's strongest in the last 500.
It's his race to lose now.
[Teagan] Come on, Cam! Push!
Go, Ryder!
[Madison] Ryder's taking over.
[Teagan] That doesn't make any sense.
Cam can push harder than this.
Yes! Go, Ryder!
Come on, Cam!
[Madison] Head in the game!
[Hayden] Let's go, boys! Keep it up!
[straining]
-[buzzer sounds]
-Yes!
-Let's go!
-[crowd cheering]
Yes! Go, Ryder!
[woman] The winner
from Easton Prep, Ryder Regis.
[Hayden] Way to go!
-[shuddering and gasping]
-[Hayden] Way to go, team! Yes!
-Yes.
-[panting] Beat you.
Barely.
[uneasy music playing]
Hey, nice job.
You got a few minutes to chat?
Of course.
-Hey, what happened out there?
-I don't know what you're talking about.
Cam. Okay, you've been hitting
under a 6:20 for months.
It was yours, and then you just quit.
Guess I choked.
No, not you. Not when an invite
to the Junior National tryouts
is on the line.
That's Olympic track.
-What, did you throw the race?
-Teagan, mind your business.
What are you doing?
A bad score will follow you
for the rest of your career.
Ryder is out talking to the scout.
-That should be you. Do you understand?
-Of course I do.
-Then why?
-Because some things are more important.
Like what?
[melancholy music playing]
The shop's going under
and I needed the money.
Did someone pay you to throw the race?
[groans]
-It was Ryder. Oh, Cam.
-No.
-I knew you would understand.
-There had to be a better way.
It was $48,000, Teagan. How was I
supposed to get that kind of money?
-I don't know, I…
-Then just focus on your own race.
I'm missing Teagan's competition for this.
Explain.
Every new hotel bled money.
My CFO stole investor funds
to pay off all the old debts.
But it wasn't just debts.
You took money for yourself,
for us, our home, our life.
You want to know how I know?
They took everything back,
including the education fund.
El, I'm sorry.
I've been breaking my back
to keep us going.
I never should have been gone so long.
My partner made it look like
it was only me, so I had to run.
I just needed time to find him
so I could fix things.
And now I can. With this.
This USB has evidence against him,
and I hid it with one of Teagan's medals.
[Ella] Are you serious?
What happens next?
Are you gonna give that to the FBI?
No. Because it also has
evidence against me.
-[Ella sighs]
-My deal's with my partner,
and he's willing to pay me
a lot of money for this USB.
How does this fix anything?
It'll set you and Teagan up.
-You can use the money to go back to LA.
-I don't want to leave, David.
Teagan and I…
We've built a life here.
What are you gonna do?
If I turn myself in,
I could go to jail for 20 years.
I can't do that, Ella.
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
Keep running then.
I wanna see Teagan.
You don't get to see Teagan.
Not until you make things right,
and this is not making things right.
-Your heat's in ten.
-Thank you.
Hey, Madison, uh, I need a favor.
Our parents might be bedfellows,
but I don't think we're there just yet.
It's for Cam, and you can't ask why.
Just know I wouldn't be asking
if it wasn't important.
You saw what happened with him.
Okay, what can I do?
I need you
to put me on the same erg as Cam.
[intriguing music playing]
Okay.
[woman] Next race, U17 Women.
All rowers, pick up the handle.
-Did Teagan switch ergs?
-I'm not keeping track.
[woman] Sit ready.
-Attention… Go!
-[buzzer sounds]
["Muscle" by METTE playing]
♪ What's underneath is real, I'm sure ♪
♪ What you've got's impressive ♪
♪ It caught my attention ♪
Looking good, Teag.
You got this! You got this!
♪ Don't waste my time
'Cause time ain't free ♪
♪ Just cross the line and step to me ♪
♪ Pump it up
Electric ♪
♪ Make the cut
'Cause I get what I want ♪
She's dropping.
Come on, Teagan. You're faster than this.
Maybe she's just having an off day?
[Cam] Come on!
[Madison] You got it!
[grunts]
She's working hard,
but running out of time.
[Cam] What is she up to?
-[buzzer sounds]
-[woman] The winner is Lara Robinson.
[grunts]
Twelfth. She's not gonna like that.
Uh…
There's, uh, something wrong with my erg.
What's she doing?
[woman] You called me over?
What happened out there?
There was something wrong with my erg.
It probably affected your race as well.
Teagan, what did you do?
[quiet, tense music playing]
Nothing.
Okay, well, Teagan, you were right.
The judges determined there was
an obstruction on the drivetrain,
so they're gonna take the erg
out of the rest of the races.
-What about our scores?
-You can't race again today.
You wouldn't have the energy.
So they've agreed
to strike your scores from the record.
I'm sorry, guys.
I know how much
you wanted to impress this scout,
but it is what it is.
They will set up a time for you to re-row.
That's gonna be set
by the president of the jury, okay?
-Okay.
-[Hayden] Okay?
Thank you.
[woman] No. It's sticking.
We're gonna have to replace
the whole thing.
What the hell, Teagan?
-Okay.
-Look, you shouldn't have done that.
You were about to throw away
everything you worked for, Cam.
Yeah, but that was my choice.
You threw away your chance with the scout.
-Yeah, well, that was mine.
-Look, I told you to stay out of this.
You were the one who said there are
more important things than rowing,
and you know what? You are right.
You. You are more important.
You need to stay out of my mess.
[melancholy music playing]
-[phone buzzing]
-[sighs]
[beeps]
Hey.
[Hayden] Hey.
So I've got some good news
and some bad news.
Bad news is Teagan's race
got scratched today,
but she will get a chance to re-race.
And the good news?
The good news is she is open to us dating.
Ish. With some minor restrictions.
About that, um…
I think we need to put things on hold.
Oh.
Uh…
Is-is-is everything okay?
Did I do something?
No, it's definitely not you.
I just need to be alone right now.
Okay.
If that's what you want,
that's what you need, um…
I guess, take care of yourself, El.
[Logan] Nice job, man. I saw you in there,
you looked pretty good.
Thanks, you were looking good too.
-[Logan] It went well.
-Hey!
Right on.
Watch this one.
He's cute, enjoys late night chats.
-And stabbing you in the back.
-Excuse me. What is your problem?
Don't pretend, it's insulting.
-You ghosted me.
-Because you sabotaged us at the regatta.
What?
You asked me to hook up in the boathouse.
And when I left you,
you cut Josh's oar
so it would snap during the race.
Girl, do you know
how crazy you sound right now?
Don't play dumb. I know it was you.
You know, I replayed that day.
Over and over again in my head.
I'm trying to understand
why you blocked me.
Hey, what changed? What would make
this incredible guy start to hate me?
Turns out, you believed
I was capable of the worst things.
Good to know, I guess.
But…
It had to be you.
You were alone in there, and you were
the only one who could've done it.
You wanted to leave first.
You asked me to wait five minutes
before I left, so I did.
And I wasn't even alone in there.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-What do you mean?
As I was leaving, I heard
somebody coming through the window.
They didn't see me, but…
I saw them.
It was your stroke. Josh.
You!
-You goddamn liar, you lied to my face.
-Whoa, Loo.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-The oar.
You did it.
And you let Logan take the fall for it.
Look, it's not what you think.
You watched me break up with him.
You psychopath!
I wanted to tell you.
-But you didn't.
-Hold on, Baloo. What's going on?
Baloo, come on.
You know what you did.
And soon, everyone else will know
you sabotaged the race.
[tense music playing]
What is he talking about?
-None of your business.
-Josh.
Teagan, get away from my car.
No. Not until you tell me what's going on.
Fine.
[engine roaring]
-[Teagan] What was Baloo talking about?
-[Josh] Just leave it alone.
Did you cut the oar?
Oh my God.
Why is everyone always on my case?
Just answer me! Did you or didn't you?
Everybody wants a piece of me.
And then why does everybody
need me to do something that I can't do?
Hey, hey, Josh…
No, nothing is ever enough!
-I don't think you're okay. We should…
-No, I'm fine, okay? I'm…
-[stammering] I have to be fine. I…
-Josh.
[Josh grunts in pain]
-Josh?
-[groans]
-[tires screech]
-[screams]
[Teagan groans]
[panting]
Oh my gosh! Josh! Josh, Josh!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
-Whoa. Hey.
-You're okay.
-You blacked out. We went off the road.
-What's going on?
-But I just…
-What?
-I don't think you're okay. I'll call 911.
-Teagan, your head.
-You're gonna go to the hospital.
-What?
-No. Wait!
-Stay here. Okay? Hold on.
-No…
-We're gotta call someone.
-What if you black out again?
-Wait one sec!
That's why we can't call anyone.
-[Josh] Oh shit.
-Okay.
-Oh, shit, this is really bad.
-[Teagan] This is serious.
We've gotta call someone. I'm gonna…
Wait! No. No, no, no!
-What are you doing?
-I'm thinking, okay?
What is there to think about?
[grunting in pain]
[gasping and shuddering]
You're sick, aren't you?
The pills that you took at your party,
is that part of it? And then the sabotage?
[Josh, crying] Yeah, I am.
[sniffles]
I have a heart condition.
It's getting worse.
Well…
Are you gonna have a heart attack?
Do your parents know?
No, I can't tell them.
Everything's a competition.
They can't…
-They can't know that their son's…
-What?
[Josh panting]
Hey, what?
Defective.
They won't think that.
They only love me if I win.
When you fail in my family,
the sun just stops shining on you.
When Ryder got stroke seat,
he got my internship.
And now he's going to be
making the junior national team,
and I'm next to my messed up car!
I can't hide this.
I know, I know it's dysfunctional, I just…
I still don't want to let down my dad.
[somber music playing]
You have to see a doctor
and tell your parents
before you seriously hurt yourself.
I know. It's just…
Easton's hosting the Haverford Cup.
My granddad's gonna be there,
and all of his buddies
are gonna be watching, and…
I wanna show my family my best
before I tell them.
Give me one last regatta
before I walk away.
Okay, I know how to buy you some time.
But you have to see a doctor.
Okay.
I know someone who can fix this.
[vehicle approaching]
I need a favor.
[intriguing music playing]
[music ends]